$SimplyKnockSettingsPage	Settings
$SimplyKnockSaveLoadPage	Profiles

$SimplyKnockHeaderSettings	Settings
$SimplyKnockSaveLoadHeaderProfile	Settings Profiles

$SimplyKnockSettingsSuccessChance	Base Success Chance
$SimplyKnockSettingsTimeoutDuration	Request Failure Timeout
$SimplyKnockSettingsFriendsAllowEntry	Friends Always Allow Entry
$SimplyKnockSaveLoadCurrentProfile	Current Profile:
$SimplyKnockSaveLoadAboutProfiles	About Settings Profiles
$SimplyKnockSaveLoadEnable	Automatic Profile Save / Load
$SimplyKnockSaveLoadRenameProfile	Rename Profile
$SimplyKnockSkyUI51Required	SkyUI 5.1+ Required
$SimplyKnockSaveLoadDefaultProfile	Default Current Profile
$SimplyKnockSaveLoadSettingsSaved	All settings saved successfully.

$SimplyKnockSettingsSuccessChanceHighlight	The base chance of how often you will succeed in requesting to come inside, unmodified by Speechcraft skill. Speechcraft adds 0.5% chance per point of Speechcraft.\nDefault: 50%.
$SimplyKnockSettingsTimeoutDurationHighlight	How long before you can try to request entry at a given location again after failure. Adjusting this setting also adjusts how long you will be permitted to stay once granted entry, so setting this to a very low value is not recommended.\nDefault: 24 hours.
$SimplyKnockSettingsFriendsAllowEntryHighlight	If enabled, friends will always allow you to enter.\nDefault: Enabled.
$SimplyKnockOptionHighlightSettingSelectProfile	Select a Settings Profile where all of your Simply Knock settings will be saved automatically.\nSettings Profiles are written to a file and persistent across saves, loads, characters, and new games.\nYour last used Settings Profile will be loaded for you when the game starts (if enabled).
$SimplyKnockOptionHighlightSettingRenameProfile	Rename the current Settings Profile.
$SimplyKnockOptionHighlightSettingDefaultProfile	Restore the current profile to default settings.
$SimplyKnockOptionHighlightSettingEnableSaveLoad	Enable or disable saving your settings to a Settings Profile and loading your current profile when the game starts.\nIf disabled, your settings will no longer be saved or loaded automatically.\nSee "About Settings Profiles" for more information.

$SimplyKnockSaveLoadDefaultProfileConfirm	Are you sure you want to restore all settings on your current profile to their default values?
$SimplyKnockSaveLoadConfirm	Load the selected profile?
$SimplyKnockSaveLoadRenameErrorBlank	The profile name cannot be blank.

$SimplyKnockSaveLoadTopic	Settings Profiles store all of your Simply Knock configuration settings to a file. Each time you change a setting, that change is automatically saved to your current profile.\n\nWhen you load your game, switch characters, or even start a new game, your last selected profile's settings will automatically be loaded for you. This means less time configuring mods and more time playing the game.
$SimplyKnockSaveLoadTopicCont	You can have more than one profile, and you can name your profiles to make it easier to remember which settings you have stored. There are 10 profile slots available to use. This makes it easy to have saved settings for many different characters and playstyles.\n\nTo turn off this behavior, disable "Automatic Profile Save / Load". Your settings will no longer be saved when changed or loaded on start-up.
$SimplyKnockSaveLoadTopicCont2	Your settings are saved to /skyrim/Data/SKSE/Plugins/SimplyKnockData/. The common.json and profile*.json files contain your profile settings.\n\nIf you use Mod Organizer, your settings will most likely be saved to [Mod Organizer Directory]/overwrite/SKSE/Plugins/SimplyKnockData.

$SimplyKnockSettingsUseAltMenu	Use Alternate Door Menu
$SimplyKnockSettingsUseAltMenuHighlight	Use an alternate menu when clicking on doors. This menu will never show the destination of the door (to ensure compatibility with mods like Address Unknown), but may be less compatible with other mods that override door activation than the normal door menu.\nDefault: Disabled